https://www.sirstampalot.co.uk/privacy.php

Basket Contents My Account
FREE 1st Class UK postage on orders over £10
Home
|  What's New?
Home » Privacy Notice
Sir Stampalot is Committed to Protecting Your Privacy.
We
respect your privacy and we are committed to protecting your personal data and
complying with requirements of the General Data Protection Act 2018. This
privacy policy will tell you how we look after your personal data when you
visit Sir Stampalot in person or via our website.
We
hope you'll find these updates improve your customer experience and reinforce
our commitment to your data privacy and security.
This
information regarding our Privacy Policy is made easily accessible by providing
a link at the bottom of all pages within the Sir Stampalot website.
Changes in our Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any
time. Such variations become effective immediately upon posting to the website
and by continuing to use the website, you will be deemed to accept any such
variations.
Collecting Personal Information
Sir Stampalot cares
about your privacy. For this reason, we collect and use personal data, when
voluntarily submitted by you, only as it might be needed for us to deliver to
you, our exceptional services and crafty products.
The personal data required
to fulfil such services include:
notes or details explaining what you asked and
how we responded - ie. always send items via courier rather than royal mail.
Your payment method for an order, ie. credit card, PayPal - method only not card details
Using Personal Information
We strongly believe in both minimising the data we collect
and limiting its use and purpose to only that:
(1) for which we have been given permission,
We need to process your personal data as outlined in the
previous section above (Collecting Personal Information), so that we can:
send you a welcoming email to the email address
you.ve specified, once you register on our website
Send you goods purchased through our website
Supply to you services purchased through our website
Process such orders and any refunds;
Deliver goods to your specified delivery address;
Communicate with you about your account or the products/services required;
Communicate with you in emergencies or in relation to a product recall or workshop
rescheduling;
Notify you of any events that may affect your order status
Sending you our email newsletter and offers if
you have requested it (refer to the next section 'Newsletters')
We may use the information you
provide in any feedback or product reviews to improve our products and services
Newsletters
This section explains the choices you have when it comes to
receiving marketing communications from Sir Stampalot.
If you wish to subscribe to our newsletters, we will use
your name and email address to send the newsletter to you.  When you register with us we will ask if you
would like to subscribe to our newsletter 'Smudges'.
We'll never bombard you with too many
communications.  We will send you
relevant offers and news about our products and services only if you have
previously agreed to receive these marketing communications.
If you would prefer to stop receiving them at any
time, please do tell us - simply click on the unsubscribe link in any of our email newsletters, contact our Customer Services team on 01733 324 007 or email support@sirstampalot.co.uk.
Just to let you know though, that even if you unsubscribe
from our newsletter so you don.t receive any more marketing info, please note
that we may still be required to send you emails regarding transactions and
services we provide you for instances when you place an order with us online,
we will send you a confirmation email and then another email at time of
despatch so you know your order is on its way to you.
Disclosing Personal Information
You can visit the majority of our website without revealing
any personal information.   All information on visitors collected by us is used
exclusively by Sir Stampalot and is not otherwise distributed, disclosed, sold,
rented, traded or used for any other purpose. The information is collected by
our servers to help us maintain and improve the website and services to
you.
We may be legally obliged to disclose your personal
information to the extent that we are required to do so by law.  In connection with any ongoing or prospective legal proceedings - The information
is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Security of Personal Information
Sir Stampalot is committed to ensuring the security of your
information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure and to ensure the
appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate electronic and
administrative procedures to secure the information we collect online.
We use computer safeguards such as firewalls, data
encryption, a private network and we enforce physical access controls to our
building and files to keep this data safe.
Access to your personally identifiable information is kept secure and is
limited to specific authorised personnel.
Sir Stampalot continually reviews and up-dates its security
procedures as new technologies become available and new activities are
introduced.
Payment Details
Online Orders
We'd like to reassure you that our payment server is
completely secure and at no point are your card details seen by us, nor are
they kept on file.   All details of
financial transactions entered via our website are protected by encryption
technology as we use, as our third party payment processors, the world-renowned:
Sage Pay (privacy policy for Sage Pay is
available in full at https://www.paypal.com/uk/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full)
and
Paypal (privacy policy for PayPal is available
in full at https://www.paypal.com/uk/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full)
Both Sage Pay and PayPal, notify us only of the amount paid,
date of transaction, your name, address, delivery details and payment reference.  In case of refund, PayPal also informs us of
the email address assigned to that PayPal account.  This email is never recorded separately
outside of PayPal and never used, other than for the purpose of returning funds
to your PayPal account.
Phone Orders
When placing orders over the phone with Sir Stampalot, and
verbally notifying us of your payment details for an order, we do not retain
your credit card information after processing the payment.
Accuracy of Personal Information
We will make every effort to ensure that any information we
hold will be accurate and up to date.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you
is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible,
and we will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Your Rights
You are in control
- We provide you with the tools to control your account information and
guidance on how it is used. Simply access your online account and go to 'My
Account Information' to:
View and update your account information such as name, email address, phone number
and billing address.
View and update your contact preferences for receiving account and product related
messages and marketing communications.
All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt
out of further mailings.
You may instruct us to provide you with any personal
information we hold about you at any time.
Upon receipt of such a request we will, after confirming identity,
provide all relevant data we may hold to you in the most practical format
unless otherwise stipulated and reasonably possible.
If you instruct is to no longer process your personal data,
we will do so as quickly as possible.
If you instruct us to destroy any/all of your personal data
we may hold, we will do so as quickly as possible.
If you instruct us to cease all processing for marketing
purposes, we will do so as quickly as possible.
If you are unable for any reason to access your Account
Settings or our Privacy Policy, you may also contact us:
Email: support@sirstampalot.co.uk
Telephone: 01733 324 007
Business Transitions
In the event that Sir Stampalot goes through a business
transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company or sale of all or
a portion of its assets, your personal information will likely be among the
assets transferred.   We will ensure that these security
practices are kept and reasonable precautions to protect the transferred
information are put in place.
Links to Other Websites
Please note that where we provide links to other sites, they
may not be governed by this Privacy Policy and you should view the particular
privacy policies of those sites for further information as once you have used
these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control
over that other website.
Hmmmm Cookieeees
Unfortunately not
the edible sort ;(
A cookie, in
relation to websites, is a piece of information asking permission to be
placed on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are generally used to store
information and, when used correctly, their use adds functionality to a
website.
www.sirstampalot.co.uk,
like almost every other website, uses cookies to give you a better online
experience.  They are used to save
time and make visiting web sites more efficient and enjoyable.  This includes remembering login information
to what is in your online shopping basket.
There is lots of guidance out there explaining what cookies
are and what they can do. We are going to explain how cookies affect the Sir
Stampalot website, but if you want more information you can visit: http://www.allaboutcookies.org
In line with recent changes in EU law, the following table
lists the cookies Sir Stampalot collects and what information the cookies
store.
Cookie Name
Cookie Description
__utma
__utmz
Google Analytics: We use Google Analytics to monitor traffic levels, search queries and visits to our
website.  The cookies collect
information such as the number of visitors to the site and where visitors have
come from geographically and throughout the web.  Both Sir Stampalot and
Google Analytics stores IP address data anonymously and
neither Sir Stampalot nor Google associate your IP address with any
personally identifiable information.
By using our site, you are giving your consent to the use of these cookies.
Visit the Privacy Policy of Google to find out further information about these cookies (https://policies.google.com/privacy/update).
osCsid
Your session id on the Sir Stampalot server.
This is an essential cookie to the operation of the site that is always set when you connect to our site.  For instance, it
remembers the items in your shopping cart whilst browsing other parts of Sir Stampalot.
This is used to carry information throughout your journey on the website.  It does not contain any personal information and is encrypted.
This cookie is deleted when the browser is closed or if the session times out after 20 minutes.
If you choose to disable some or all Cookies, you may not be able to make full use of our Sir Stampalot website. For example, you may not be
able to add items to your shopping basket, proceed to checkout, or use any of our products and services that require you to sign in.
Social Media Services - Our 'share product' feature of our web site may connect with some social media services for instance Facebook.
These may use third party cookies to connect with your own Facebook
account. However, we do NOT have any direct access to information relating to your Facebook account.
For details on Facebook's privacy policy please visit https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation
Data Protection Officer
We value your opinions. If you have comments or questions
about this Privacy Policy or if you have any unresolved privacy or data use
concerns that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our Data
Protection officer (DPO):
Email: admin@sirstampalot.co.uk
By
Telephone: 01733 324 007
In writing to: Data
Protection Officer, Sir Stampalot, 72 Papyrus Road, Peterborough, PE4 5BH
We aim to respond to all requests, enquiries or concerns
within fourteen (14) days.
Our
Privacy Policy does not affect your statutory rights as a consumer.
This page was last updated: 23rd May 2018
Continue
Categories
SALE ITEMS
Accessories
Cardstock & Paper
Die Cutting & Punching
Inspiration
Tim Holtz
Manufacturers Please SelectAmerican ArtstampArt ImpressionsBasic GreyBazzill BasicsBo BunnyClearsnapCopicCrafters CompanionCrafts TooCreate and Craft TVCreative ExpressionsDina WakleyDolphin SongDovecraftEK SuccessFiskarsGreat ImpressionsHampton ArtHero ArtsHobby ArtHobby HouseImpression ObsessionInkadinkadooJudikinsK and CompanyLasting ImpressionsMagentaMagnolia StampsMaking MemoriesMartha StewartMiscellaneousMolly Blooms by ClareMy Favourite ThingsOutlines Rubber StampsPebbles Inc.Penny BlackPersonal ImpressionsPrickley PearProvocraftRanger InksRubber SoulRubber Stamp TapestrySakuraSir StampalotSizzixStampendousStampington & CompanyTimeless TouchesTombowTsukinekoUS ArtQuestWhipper SnapperWild Rose StudioWoodwareYour Next Stamp Shopping Cart 0 items
Specials TC Floral Heart£12.95£4.00
Reviews a good fun sized stamp and stamps up really well .. 5 of 5 Stars!
Shipping & Returns Privacy Notice Conditions of Use Contact Us
Copyright © 2002-2020 sirstampalot.co.uk
All Rights Reserved.
